歡迎 你們大多知道我代理副校長塔克的身份
Welcome. Most of you know me as Acting Vice Principal Tucker,
但是今天...
but today...
我是你們通往未來的指引者...
I am your guide to the future...
未來... 未來...
the future... the future.
好吧 所以你在回音上沒聽我的建議
Okay, so you didn't take my note on the echo.
米奇爾 我腦子聽不進更多的負面評論了
Mitchell, I can't take another negative voice in my head.
我已經被布朗校長嚇懵了
I'm already freaking out about Principal Brown.
我有種被校園霸凌的感覺
I kind of have a bully at school.
你要把這都吃完嗎
You gonna eat all that?
我 我想不是吧
I-I guess not.
那好
Okay.
看到你關于明天研討會的計劃了
Saw your plans for the seminar tomorrow.
你喜歡嗎 你知道 我覺得孩子們
Oh, you like it? Y-You know, I think the kids
聽一聽四個路途迥異的畢業生的發言
will really benefit from hearing from four graduates
一定會感覺獲益匪淺的
that have taken such different paths.
他們中有上傳統大學的 也有空檔一年的...
I've got traditional college, gap year --
大錯特錯 我們只推行一條路 上大學
Wrong! We're pushing one path here -- college.
行吧 好 但大學才不是
Well, yeah, but college isn't necessarily
對每個人來說的必經...
the right path for every--
塔克 你熟悉"金蘋果"這個詞嗎
Tucker, are you familiar with the term "Golden Apple"?
熟悉啊 我有點驚訝
I am. I'm a little surprised
這個用語進入了普通直男世界
it's made its way into the straight vernacular.
這玩法在阿拉巴馬州還是非法的呢
It's still illegal in Alabama.
不不不 金蘋果是個獎項 授予給那些
No, no, no, Golden Apple status is awarded to schools
大學錄取率在60%以上的學校
that reach a minimum of 60% college acceptance.
如果我們不夠 我就得回去在夜校教書了
If we dip below that, I'm back to teaching night school.
如果你認為學校的午餐阿姨很兇殘的話
If you think the lunch ladies are mean,
那晚餐阿姨就是殘上加殘了
you should meet the dinner ladies.
行 但其他學生...
Yeah, but what about the students that --
合作[玩球] 代理副校長塔克
Play ball, Acting Vice Principal Tucker,
或許你會發現自己變成了...
and you might just find yourself --
副校長嗎
Vice principal?
我只是不確定我是不是能說動別人
I just don't know if I can preach something
聽信一些我自己都不相信的事情
that I don't believe.
-"合作" -這詞以前沒人用
- Ha! Play ball. - Seems like a thing
現在倒是大紅大紫了
no one was saying, and now everyone is.
你知道我在做什么嗎
You know what I'm doing right now?
我在做一百個小蛋糕
I'm making 100 cupcakes
因為地檢官孩子派對的承辦人跑了
because the D.A. lost his caterer for his kid's party
他問我能不能幫忙
and asked if I could help out.
但是如果這能讓他對我多加青睞的話
But if it puts me, uh, higher up on his radar,
那我就做吧
then so be it.
我只是說有時候你得妥協
I'm just saying sometimes you need to compromise
以退為進
to -- to get ahead.
也許我們的時代到來了
Maybe it's our time now.
我喜歡
Ooh, I like that.
你好 世界 一對強權夫夫正在冉冉升起
Hey, world, there's a new power couple on the horizon.
對
Yeah.
小卡和米奇
Cam and Mitch.
卡奇... 不 聽起來好怪
Citch -- No, that sounds weird.
米姆[女士]...
Mam --
以后會想到的
We'll find it.
爸爸 我們的視頻會議快要開始了
Hey, Dad, our video conference is about to start.
我們能快點嗎 我還要出去開銷售會議
Can we make it fast? I have that sales meeting offsite.
所以得穿著戰袍 帶著雪茄
Hence the power threads and box of cigars.
爸爸 現在才上午十點
Whoa! Dad, it's 10:00 in the morning.
我不會咽的
I don't swallow it.
他聞到我身上的酒氣就會放松警惕
He smells it on my breath, he lets his guard down.
只要二十分鐘 他就隨我玩弄
In 20 minutes, I'm taking him
把他玩到連"見多識廣"的獄警看到都會臉紅
in a way that would make a prison guard blush.
這是紳士們談生意的方法
It's the way gentlemen do business.
那很抱歉我打擾了您的威士忌雅興
Well, I am sorry to ruin your Glengarry, Glenlivet fun,
但那個會議被取消了
but that meeting got canceled.
什么 我還盼著呢
What? I was looking forward to it.
今天早上尼克通過網絡電話把它搞定了
Nick took care of it by Skype this morning.
登錄吧 咱們的會議要開始了
Log on. Our meeting's about to start.
好了 我們開始吧
Okay, let's begin.
尼克 咱們關于互動衣柜
So, Nick, where are we
語音指令的事情進行到哪一步了
with the interactive closet with the voice prompts?
這里有份樣本
Here's a demo.
用了與克里斯托弗·沃肯[演員]近似的聲音
Went with a Christopher Walken soundalike voice.
預報說...寒冷
Forecast is...chilly.
穿上...一些褲子
Put...on some pants.
可能是因為當時我們都喜歡"步入式衣帽間"
I think we all fell in love with the idea of calling it
與那個演員名的諧音哏 但這聲音真的不搭
a Walken closet, but this just isn't working.
克萊爾 我怎么沒看到你爸來開會呢
Hey, Claire, I don't see your dad on the video conference.
媽的
Damn it!
我電腦又壞了
My computer's busted again.
或者你的大寫鎖定又開了
Or your caps lock is on.
我們就不能在會議室開會嗎
Can't we have this meeting in the conference room?
我們都圍著桌子坐下
You know, where we all sit around a table,
面前擺著豐盛的早餐
there's a nice breakfast spread?
我厭倦了總把奶油干酪鎖在抽屜里
I am tired of having to keep cream cheese in my desk.
爸爸 你知道我們為什么要這么做
Dad, you know why we do it this way.
我們有員工在這里工作
We have people working here.
也有員工在家工作
We've got people working from home.
我們有在世界各地工作的員工
We've got people working all over the world.
蒂芙尼還在柏林的德國衣柜展呢
Tiffany is in Berlin at KlausetSchvarg.
這個展還在啊
They still have that conference?
我還以為在80年代東德衣柜展時期
I thought they shut that down in the '80s
我們用那個毛衣柜把持不同政見者偷運出去后
after we used that sweater hutch to smuggle that dissident out
那個展就從此被取消了呢
during East KlausetSchvarg.
被你發現了 記得說話對著攝像頭說
You're good. Just talk into the camera.
很抱歉剛才的事
Hoo! Sorry about that.
好的 我們的3D打印有沒有進展呢
All right. How about an update on our 3-D printing?
我想大家都認識愛德華多吧
I think everybody knows Eduardo.
杰 你倆見面了嗎
Jay, have you two met?
我看不見攝像頭
I can't see the camera!
爸爸 你在...
Dad, you're, uh...
你有點擋住鏡頭了
you're kind of smushed up against it.
你也許應該往后退一點
You might want to just step back a skosh.
使用3D打印機去制造我們的衣柜
Using a 3-D printer to manufacture our closets
能增加三倍的收益
will triple revenue.
我聽不到你們說話
I can't hear you!
音量調大 爸爸
Volume up, Dad.
僅在第一年...
In our first year alone --
搞什么鬼
What the hell?!
爸爸 "撤銷" 就...
Dad, "undo." Just --
我知道 我知道
I know! I know!
雙擊
Double-click.
? 生日快樂 ?
♪ Happy birrrthday ♪
? 衣柜先生 ?
♪ Mr. Closet -- ♪
別 別
No! No!
你們自己開這蠢會吧 我要離開這里
Have your stupid meeting! I'm outta here!
瑪格麗特 我要去街對面的公園
Margaret, I'm going to the park across the street.
我去走走
I need a walk!
真是太感謝你幫喬的忙了
Thank you so much for helping out with Joe.
你不會覺得這樣太華麗嗎
You don't think it's too flashy?
你說什么呢 你可要上的可是魔術課
What are you talking about? You're taking a magic class.
得表現出你是認真的
You want to show them you're serious.
是魔法師 不是無聊師
It's abracadabra, not abraca-drab-ra.
看那邊 公開選角征集令
Look at that! An open casting call.
打擾一下 這是選什么角色
Excuse me, what is this for?
我們在為格倫谷購物中心尋找真實家庭
We are looking for real families to be the new faces
當新的代言人
of the Glen Valley Mall.
你們都挺不錯 想報名嗎
You guys are adorable. Want to sign up?
我們不是真的是一家
Oh, we're not a-a real --
我們愿意
Oh, we would love to!
這么好的事剛巧趕上了
What a cool and a spontaneous thing to do!
我一個星期前就看到海報了
I saw that poster last week.
讓我想起了很久以前
It kind of reminded me of a long time ago
我客串當模特的時候
when I used to do a little modeling.
可能我挺懷念那時候
I guess I miss it.
我把菲爾騙到商場
I tricked Phil into going to the mall
因為我知道杰不會和我試鏡的
because I knew that Jay wouldn't do it with me.
來吧 這會很有意思的
Oh, come on, guys. This is gonna be so much fun.
我不確定
I don't know.
我們班的一個小孩拍了止咳糖漿的廣告
This kid in my class did a cough syrup commercial.
現在他總是去教師休息室
Now he's always going to the teachers' lounge
給經紀人打電話
to call his manager.
他最討厭了
He's the worst.
我五點鐘有一節房地產課要上
And I teach a real-estate class at 5:00.
我需要早點過去做準備
I have to show up early to limber up.
我覺得這對喬的自尊大有好處
I think that this could help a lot with Joe's self-esteem.
他這周過得很不順
He's had a rough week.
你知道同齡人怎么對待喜歡魔術的孩子
You know how they treat kids that are into magic.
你告訴他等到了高中就不會那樣了
Oh, you tell him when he gets to high school, that all changes.
我可不想騙他
I don't like lying to him.
你看 我真的不擅長這種事
Look, this isn't really my thing, and I'm --
而且我最近有點生病
I'm feeling a little under the weather.
你不覺得我看起來臉色有點蒼白嗎
Don't -- Don't I look a little pale?
-我們要參加 -太好了
- We will do it! - Great.
我們的私人助理會給你們準備好衣服試鏡
Our P.A. Will set you up with wardrobe for some test shots.
你們好 需要我給你們拿點什么嗎
Hey, team. Can I get you anything?
咖啡 水 純凈水還是氣泡水
Uh, coffee? Water? Still or sparkling?
我要氣泡水
Ooh, I-I'd take a sparkling.
這位人才要氣泡水
Talent wants sparkling.
你聽到了嗎 菲爾
Did you hear that, Phil?
他們叫我們人才
They call us talent!
我們別太激動得忘形 我們還是普通...
Let's not get carried away. We're still reg--
我說要氣泡水
I said sparkling.
看起來參加的人
Well, looks like you're gonna get
不少啊 塔克
a pretty solid turnout, Tucker.
現在差不多可以了
Now close the deal.
這是什么 "接啥"
Hey, what is, uh, "Whanex"?
這年頭年輕人版本的"接下來是什么"
It's the way the kids say "What's next?"
你知道 你要想和他們拉近距離
You know, if you want to reach them,
就要學習他們的說話方式
you have to learn to speak their language.
打印店搞砸了
Massive screw-up at the print shop.
我完全不知道怎么搞砸的
I-I have no idea how it happened!
對沒錯 橫幅上應該寫...
Yeah, that's right. The banner should read...
接啥 好
whanex. Okay.
對 接啥
Yeah, whanex.
歡迎同學們來到第一屆年度"接啥"研討會
Welcome, students, to the first annual "Whanex" seminar.
我們直接步入正題 歡迎今天的座談嘉賓們
Let's, uh, just jump right into it and meet our panelists.
我們邀請了兩位選擇走入大學的優秀青年
We have two bright, young people who chose the college path
還有兩個任性的迷途青年
and two wayward souls
但愿我們能從他們身上吸取教訓
whose mistakes we can only hope to learn from.
你們好 海豚隊
Sup, Dolphins?
尼克 對我爸早上的事我很抱歉
Nick, I'm so sorry about my dad this morning.
-你們好 -沒事的 別想了
- Hi. - Please forget it.
我們現在有個更大的問題
We've got a bigger problem.
我們需要為虛擬衣柜助手找個新的聲音
We have to find a new voice for the virtual closet assistant.
我們考慮 女聲
We're thinking...female.
我自己也在考慮
Yeah, I was wondering about that myself.
等一等
Hold on a second.
克萊爾有一副好嗓音 又威嚴又誘人
Claire has a great voice -- commanding but alluring.
哪有 我可不知道什么
Oh, come on. I don't know about...
誘人
...alluring.
你說得沒錯
You're right.
你說得對 我完全能聽出來
You're right. I can totally hear it.
大伙 大伙
Guys, guys...
你們說得我都不好意思了
...you're embarrassing me.
你的這一面一直藏在哪了
Where have you been hiding this?
半小時內 我給新的智能衣柜錄完了
Within half an hour, I had recorded all the voice prompts
所有的語音指令 然后他們把語音裝入了
for the new smart-closet, and they installed it
辦公室的樣品柜里
in the prototype right in the office.
大家都很高興 但是我不是很理解
Everyone seemed really happy, but I don't get it.
我是說
I mean...
聲音就是聲音而已
...A voice is just a voice.
太好了 爸 你回來了
Oh, good. Dad, you're back.
請移步我們的新型智能樣品衣柜里
Please step into our new smart-closet prototype.
方便你罵我上午不參加會議嗎
So you can yell at me for bailing on the meeting this morning?
進去就知道了
Just -- You'll see.
我能幫你選件外套嗎
May I help choose an outfit for you?
因為我是那種還在
Cause I'm some old fossil
穿西裝上班的老古董嗎
that still puts on a suit to go to work?
讓我們重新開始
Let's start over.
來就來
Why don't we?!
你想要哪種程度的舒適感
What level of comfort are you looking for?
跟我過去四十年一模一樣的那種
Same thing I've had for the last 40 years --
一個能時不時和真人交流的辦公場所
a workplace where you interact with actual people
就像我們現在這樣
every once in a while, like we're doing right now.
我以前很喜歡銷售電話
I used to love sales calls.
現在我們都不這樣推銷了
Now we don't even do them anymore.
我的意思是 你換位思考一下
I mean, put yourself in my shoes.
正裝還是休閑
Dress or casual?
為什么你聽起來像勞倫·白考爾[老明星]
Why do you sound like Lauren Bacall?!
我聽不明白
I don't understand.
對 因為現在 就像所有的東西一樣
Right, because now, like everything,
我說的梗也過時跟不上你們了
my references are old and out of step.
你為什么在吼
Why are you yelling?
你現在還不懂的話 你永遠都不會懂了
If you don't get it by now, you're never gonna get it!
有人又玻璃心了[內褲卡屁股]
Well, somebody's panties are in a bunch.
我可以再幫您準備一條嗎
May I offer you a different pair?
聽起來好詭異
That's just weird.
太好了
Ooh! Very good.
我有一個小時給我老板兒子的派對
I had an hour to make 100 cupcakes...
準備一百個小蛋糕
...for my boss's son's party,
但是這一切都是值得的
but it was all gonna be worth it.
他一定會很感激
He was gonna be so grateful,
下個升職的就是我
the next big promotion would be mine.
你這個忘恩負義的混蛋
You ungrateful monster!
親姐妹卻有不同的人生軌道
Two sisters, two paths.
畢業
Graduation...
生育
procreation.
一個掌控一切
The world on a string --
一個未婚先孕
a baby and no ring.
你說你為我而高興
Uh, you -- you said you were happy for me.
你說孩子會為我帶來無窮的樂趣
You said a baby would bring me limitless joy.
以及很窮的生活啊
And a limited bank account.
現在 曼尼 沒有人懷疑
Now, Manny, no one can doubt
藝術學位在現實世界的價值
the real-world value of an art degree,
但說點令人激動的日常東西吧
but talk a little bit about the exciting social scene.
這么問真有趣 我有天晚上
It's funny you ask -- I went to a wine and cheese mixer
去院長家參加美酒與起司晚會
at the Dean's house the other night.
他收集原住民的樂器
He collects instruments of indigenous people.
我們喝完最后一點濃郁的仙粉黛酒后
And by the time we killed the last bit of a chewy Zinfandel,
我們演奏的原住民樂器更像原住民"越氣"了
our jam sesh started to sound like a didgeri- don't.
謝謝
Thank you.
我能從這接著說嗎
Could I please pipe in here?
好的 請 這是艾麗克斯
Yes, please. Alex.
我真的很感謝
I genuinely appreciate
能有機會再回來
the opportunity to come back here,
這個我曾是畢業致辭的代表的學校
where I had the pleasure of serving as co-valedictorian,
為被排斥的成績好的學生
to offer a message of hope
帶來了希望 真的很開心
to those oft-marginalized overachievers out there.
我看見你們了
I...see...you.
不是我一個人起了雞皮疙瘩吧
Well, I can't be the only one with goose bumps in here.
請原諒我
Oh. Excuse me. Oh.
好的 歡迎大家提問
Yes, let's open it up for questions.
前排那位 請
Right here in the front row. Go ahead.
我還是不懂"接啥"
I still don't get "Whanex."
聽起來像我祖父母在俄勒岡的長途電話公司
It sounds like my grandparents' long-distance carrier in Oregon.
好的 你知道嗎 我得接這個電話
Okay, okay. You know what? I have to take this.
盧克 海莉 說說
Uh, Luke, Haley, talk a little bit
你們還住在父母家的感受吧
about how you still live at home with your parents.
怎么啦
Hey, what's up?
我還沒結束呢
I'm in the middle of my thing.
別聽我之前說的合作
Flip what I said before.
夸你想夸的傻蛋二人們吧
Start talking up the dummies.
什么
What?
我剛收到工作上的一條短信
Um, I just got a text from work.
我老板把那個大案子給別人了
My boss gave that big case to someone else!
同時 我還在
Meanwhile, I'm still on the hook
弄這些可惡的紙杯蛋糕
for these stupid cupcakes!
我的心跳很快 我的手沒知覺了
M-My heart is racing, my -- my hands are numb.
而且我感覺要被空氣傳染糖尿病了
Plus, I-I think I have a case of airborne diabetes!
等下 你是說我應該
Wait. Are you saying I-I should --
如果這些大學應用數據下降
Look, if those college application numbers fall,
布朗校長就會被開除
Principal Brown, he gets fired.
猜猜接下來是會當 塔克校長
Guess who's up next. Principal Tucker.
我從來不敢這么想
I've never dared dream of such a thing.
更高的薪水
More money,
更好的停車位
better parking space,
而且舞會主題將由你挑選
plus you get to pick the prom theme.
我終于能實現我的魔法湖心會主題了
I can finally make my Enchanted Bayou a reality.
好的 回聊
Okay, t-talk -- talk soon.
藝術學校最棒的是
What's great about art school
有很多老師都在行業工作
is that a lot of the faculty work in the industry.
我的電影研究教授
My film studies professor
帶我們參觀了所有的大制片廠
has led tours at every major studio.
好的 謝謝 曼尼
All right, thank you, Manny.
對于那些還醒著的各位
And for those of you still awake,
我認為我們今天都學到了 大學...
I think what we've learned here today is -- college,
就是個死胡同
a dead end.
好了 下一個
Okay, up next.
菲利普 歌洛莉亞 喬
Philip, Gloria, and Joe.
同樣的場景
Same setup.
爸爸和兒子玩接投球 媽媽擺放餐具
Dad playing catch with his son. Mom laying out a picnic.
好的 自然點 就像我不在這里
So, just real natural. Like I'm not even here.
沒問題
You got it.
別這么性感
Maybe not so sexy.
我的失誤
My bad.
他在和媽媽說話
He was talking to Mom.
你就用正常的方式擺食物
You can just lay out the food in a normal way.
收到 不會再這么出眾了
Copy that. No divas here.
她的頭也很奇怪
Her head is doing something weird.
我們能直點嗎
Can we straighten that up?
等下 各位
Hang on, guys.
他們為什么在竊竊私語
Why are they whispering?
是因為我們太老夫少妻感嗎
You think I look too young for you?
為什么 我的魚尾紋很明顯嗎
Why? Are my crow's feet showing?
我就知道化妝師遮瑕用太少
I knew makeup was going too light on the concealer.
各位 我們今天就混著搭配下試試
Guys, we're just mixing and matching today,
所以我們考慮換掉你們其中一個
so we're thinking about swapping out one of you.
不 我們是一個組的
No, we're a team.
我們進退一致
You get rid of one of us, and you lose all of us.
是那個小孩
It's the kid.
好的
Okay.
我還以為這是為了喬呢
I thought this was supposed to be for Joe.
很明顯 他太差了
Obviously, he's terrible at it,
那怎么能幫助提升他的自尊心呢
so how is that gonna help him with his self-esteem?
你好 我是泰勒
Hi, I'm Tyler.
不妙
Oh, this is not good.
泰勒 可能很快要說再見了
Tyler, don't get too comfortable.
我覺得我們需要試點不同的
I think we want to try something different.
-肖恩 你能過來下嗎 -好的
- Hey, Sean, could you step up here? - Yep.
對不起 菲爾
I'm so sorry, Phil.
不 我們想試下兩個爸爸
No, we want to look at two dads.
我不能扮演孩子啊
I can't play the kid.
看來你出局了 我們走
Looks like you're out. Here we go.
-肖恩 對吧 -沒錯 嗨
- Sean, was it? - Yeah. Hey.
-你好嗎 -還不錯
- How are you? - Good.
感受不到化學反應
Hmm. Not feeling that chemistry.
或者我們應該接吻
Maybe we should kiss?
我們還是等他們指示吧
We could just wait for them to tell us what to do.
讓我們試下肖恩和一個媽媽
Let's try Sean and a mom.
走開 菲爾
Move, Phil.
不 我們指的是莉迪亞
No, we meant Lydia.
好的 差不多了
All right, almost there.
喬 你過來試試
Hey, Joe, hop up here for me.
太棒了 這就是我們的一家人了
Yes! That's our family.
這就是我們格倫谷購物中心的新面孔
The new faces of Glen Valley Mall.
其他人可以離開了 謝謝
Everyone else can go. Thank you.
很高興和你們合作
Nice working with you guys.
我在城另一邊還有個試鏡
I have an audition across town.
什么試鏡
For what?
他們需要成年人嗎
Do they need grownups?
我們已經聽乖乖上大學的羔羊們說了很多
Alright, we've heard from our college-going sheep.
盧克 你明智地選擇空檔一年
Now, Luke, you wisely took a gap year,
找了份工作 賺了超多錢
got a job, made mad stacks,
還稍微做了投資對嗎
and invested a little, correct?
沒錯 我持有300微盧幣
Totally. I own 300 microrubels,
這是我在臉書上聽說的加密貨幣
a Russian cryptocurrency I heard about on Facebook,
目前只能用于購買一種
which currently, you can only use to buy
叫弗蘭肯斯坦的車臣派對毒品
a Chechen party drug called Frankenstein.
好吧 海莉
Okay, Haley, uh...
有性感男友 有工作 準媽媽
hot boyfriend, job, baby on the way --
感覺你人生圓滿 而你選擇的道路
You seem to have it all, yet you took a very different path
和你姐姐艾麗克斯很不一樣
than your older sister, Alex.
-我是妹妹 -是嗎 好吧
- I'm younger! - Oh, wow. Okay.
我想這就是為什么人們說如今
I guess that's why they call studying
"學習如抽煙催人老"
"The new smoking."
從沒有人這么說
No one says that.
我能不能加一句
Can I add --
你肯定能 但對現實世界又有什么幫助
I'm sure you can, but it won't help in the real world.
總之 多謝各位前來
Anyway, thank you all for coming.
大家下午愉快 保重
Have a good afternoon. Take care.
小卡 你搞什么
Cam, what the hell?
我學到了很多
I learned a lot.
塔克
Tucker!
我在滴滴上沒接到客
I wasn't picking up a lot of Uber fares,
所以我提前回來
so I came back here early
聽到了你最后這段結尾
and I heard the end of your little presentation.
我知道你打的什么小算盤
I know what you're trying to do.
我得和他談一下
Hey, I just need to talk to him for-for one second.
你猜怎么著
Hey, hey. Guess what.
我剛剛把小蛋糕送到上司家去了
I just dropped off the cupcakes at my boss's house.
原來他沒把我想接的案子給我
Turns out he-he didn't give me the case I wanted
是因為他有個更好的案子要給我
because he had an even better one for me.
真的嗎 那太好了
Really? T-that's amazing.
而且他也不是要我做小蛋糕
And he didn't want me to make cupcakes.
他只是想讓我推薦一個新承包商
He just wanted me to recommend a new caterer.
我們為此笑得前仰后合
So we had a big laugh about that.
但這都證明了
But just goes to show,
別耍小把戲
don't play games.
做好你的工作 你就會得到認可
Do your job, and you'll be recognized.
-是啊 可你說 -別管我說過什么
Yeah, but you said -- No, ah! Forget what I said.
條條大路通羅馬
T-there's no one path to success.
這才是你該教給孩子們的
I mean, that's what you should be telling these kids.
是啊 我本來是想這么跟孩子們說的
Yeah, that's what I was going to tell these kids --
去你的 塔克
Damn it, Tucker!
我的霸氣姿勢維持不了這么久
I can't hold my alpha power stance this long.
我的小腿要抽筋了
My calves are starting to cramp.
好吧 首先
Okay, well, first of all --
不 省省吧 明白嗎
No, can it! Okay?
你以為能用低大學申請率埋葬我
You thought you could bury me by killing college applications,
是不是
didn't you?
我這就去收拾和別人共用的那半張桌子
I will clean out my half of the desk that I share.
不 我很抱歉 這都是我的錯
Oh, no, it's -- I'm so sorry. T-this is-this is my fault.
我在工作上試著乖乖合作
I tried to play ball at work.
還沒必要地烤了很多蛋糕
There was a lot of unnecessary baking.
重點是 是我給了他這些想法 所以...
The point is, I-I put these ideas into his head, so...
所以你如此軟弱 沒有信念
So you're so weak and without conviction
某人向你提議一些蠢主意
that somebody suggests some stupid idea to you
你甚至不想想看 就拋棄所有價值觀
and without even thinking, you just abandon all your values
像廉價的扇子一樣任憑人折來折去
and fold like a cheap Chinese fan, huh?
是的 先生 我是只應聲蟲
Yes, sir. I am a worm.
這正是我要找的特質
That is exactly what I'm looking for.
完全不會威脅到我
No threat to me at all.
恭喜你 正式副校長塔克
Well, congratulations, permanent Vice Principal Tucker.
-真的嗎 -真的
- Really? - Yes.
謝謝您 我愛您
Thank you! I love you!
我也愛你
I love you, too.
當務之急 去彌補你剛才的過失
Now, first order of business -- fix what you did here.
你要為我摘下金蘋果
You are gonna give me a Golden Apple.
我們倆可是穩定伴侶
We are in a committed relationship!
不不不 這不是一回事
No, no, no. It's not the same thing we saw at
不是胡嬌單身漢派對上那種
Pepper's bachelor party.
-不是嗎 -不是
- It's not? - No.
和所有人吵了一整天后
After fighting with everybody all day,
我開始思考 或許 是我犯渾了
I was starting to think maybe... I was the jerk.
所以最后我回到老辦公室
So I ended up back at the old office, you know,
試圖搞清楚我究竟是為什么
trying to figure out what it was about going to work there
熱愛去那里工作
that I loved so much.
恭喜
Congratulations.
你被普里契特衣柜 百葉窗及水床雇用了
You've been hired at Pritchett's Closets, Blinds, and Waterbeds.
我是杰·普里契特
I'm Jay Pritchett.
歡迎成為團隊一員
Welcome to the team.
聽到了嗎
You hear that?
他們已經在為你歡呼了
They're cheering for you already.
我們這里很珍視一個品質 那就是團隊合作
That's something we value here -- teamwork.
無論你是銷售部還是運輸部
And whether you're in sales or shipping
或是可愛的文職人員之一
or one of those cute tomatoes in the steno pool,
你都很重要
you're important,
因為在這我們是一家人
'cause we're family here.
等一下 這個新雇員是誰
Wait a minute! Who's this new employee?
是我 克萊爾 爸爸
It's me -- Claire, Daddy.
沒錯 是克萊爾
Oh, right! It's Claire!
手真靈巧
Nice hands.
難怪我們公司的壘球隊永遠贏不了球
Reminds me why our softball team never won a game.
看看是誰從高級總部辦公室跑出來了
Look who they let out of the fancy corporate office.
你老婆有沒有突然醒悟離你而去
Hey, that wife of yours get smart and leave you yet?
她真的離我而去了 這段日子很艱難
Eh, actually, she did. It's been rough.
我們不知道 我太抱歉了
Oh. I -- We didn't know. I'm so sorry.
你們這些傻瓜 我逗你們玩的
Ah, you mutts, I'm screwing with you!
她能去哪
Where's she going?
我知道我爸心里有疙瘩
I knew my dad was going through something,
當我在舊辦公室看到他的車時
and when I saw his car at the old office,
就過來確認他狀態如何
I-I stopped by to check on him.
你羞嗎 克萊爾
Are you feeling shy, Claire?
是啊 我想是有點
Yeah, I guess I am a little.
你幾歲了
How old are you?
你說得對 我就直說了
You're right. Just come out and say it.
我擔心我們把公司賣了讓你不開心
I'm worried that you're unhappy we sold the company
并且你覺得這是我的錯
and you're blaming it on me.
你又有你要去拉粑粑的那個表情了
You're making that face like you have to go potty.
我很焦慮
I'm anxious and --
你怎么能看到我的表情啊
How can you even see my face?
她是我女兒
She's my daughter.
她認為這里她說了算
She thinks she runs the place.
你還說他不會干呢
You said he wouldn't do it.
沒錯 老子干了
You're damn right, I did it.
老大永遠都是老大啊
Boss is still the best, huh?
老爸想"家"了
My dad was homesick.
杰 你的屁股可真上相啊
That is one photogenic butt, Jay.
你帶回家吧 讓你在家還能繼續拍馬屁
Take it with you. You can kiss it at home, too.
-大家好啊 -你來啦
- Hey, guys. - Hey.
-老爸 -你怎么來這里啦
- Hi, Dad. - Hey, what are you doing here?
我看到你的車嘛
I, uh, saw your car.
聽我說
Look...
我知道你最近在工作上有點不順心
I know you've been frustrated at work lately.
不用擔心這個啦
Don't worry about that.
但你新工作上挺順利的吧
You're doing great, though, huh?
是啊 我還挺喜歡的
Yeah, I kind of love it.
但我不能只顧自己不顧你啊
But it doesn't feel right if you hate it.
老爸 這合作我們是可以甩頭就走的
Dad, we can bail on the whole thing.
你知道我真正該甩開的是什么嗎
You know what I need to bail on?
是甩開像桃子般的自己
Being such a little peach.
-什么 -一磕碰就壞嘛
- What? - They bruise easily.
我記得有這種說法 但無所謂啦
It could be an expression. I don't know.
重點是當我在這里時 我更能與人接觸
The point is, when I was here, I reached out more.
我錄了與別人問候的視頻
I made videos greeting people.
建立起了真正的感情
I built real relationships.
剛才那三個人 我能記住其中兩人的名字呢
Those three guys -- I knew two of their names.
我想或許我該試著多向你學習
I think maybe I need to try to be a little bit more like you
給這個新合作一個機會
and give this new thing a chance.
其實他們也沒那么糟啦 只要你習慣了...
You know, they're not so bad when you get past the --
他們的嬉皮士胡子還有都是手汗的握手
the hipster beards and the sweaty handshakes.
跟我說說那個打印男 愛德華多
Tell me about that printer guy, Eduardo.
3D打印到底是什么鬼
What the hell is 3-D printing anyway?
你在試著學習呢
Look at you trying.
老爸
Oh, Dad!
3D打印就是用三種激光
Okay, 3-D printing is when you take three lasers
你可以掃描任何你想要的事物
and you can scan any object you want.
然后...
You --
你想3D打印你的屁股對吧
You want to 3-D print your butt, don't you?
你想要他們喜歡我不是嗎
We want them to like me, don't we?
好了 寶貝跟小伙伴玩得開心
Okay, baby, have fun at your play date.
我兩小時后來接你
I'll pick you up in two hours.
你能相信我現在是個模特了嗎
Can you believe I'm a model now?
瘋狂世界啊
Crazy world.
再見啦 小伙子
See you, buddy.
-寶貝再見 -媽媽再見
- Bye, baby. - Bye, Mom!
天啊 我真為這孩子高興
Gosh, I'm so happy for that kid.
是啊 我們一直這么說
Yeah, we keep saying that.
我覺得自己好傻啊
I feel, uh, silly I got so invested
為永遠不會有人看到的商場海報投入靈魂
in modeling for some mall poster no one's ever gonna see.
你想感覺好一些嗎
You want to feel better?
我帶你去看個東西 看完之后
I'll show you something that is gonna make me
我保證會比你更顯可悲
look more pathetic than you do.
我說的只是"傻"吧 但...
I think I said "silly," But, um...
行啊
yeah, okay.
那是我20年前拍的
That was me 20 years ago.
很棒啊
That's amazing.
所以你不開心的原因是什么啊
But what are you so upset about?
你現在還是跟當年一樣美啊
You're just as beautiful now as you were then.
我知道啦
Aww. I know.
只是我會想起那段時光
It's just that it was a time in my life
我曾在外面坑蒙拐騙
where I was out there hustling,
當模特 開出租
modeling, driving a taxi,
在夜店外面賣培根卷熱狗
selling bacon-wrapped hot dogs outside a nightclub.
看到他們把那廣告拆下來
Seeing them taking it down made me feel like
令我感到那時的我要永遠消失了
that version of me is gone forever.
因此你又想要開始模特生涯
So that's why you wanted to start modeling again.
我只是想念對某件事物很有激情的感覺
I just miss being passionate about something again.
就像你對房地產一樣的激情
The way that you feel passionate about real estate.
你總是看起來很... 很有活力
Mm. You always seem, like, so alive,
做成新買賣 認識新的人
making new deals, meeting new people.
你有想過來當房地產中介嗎
Have you ever thought about becoming a Realtor?
-誰沒想過啊 -這倒是真的
- Who hasn't? - That's true.
我有次曾買過一本書來學怎么做這行
I bought a book one time to learn how to do it,
但你也懂后來怎么樣了
but you know how it is.
有時候人生就是會卡在一個瓶頸
Sometimes in life, you just get stuck.
我覺得你很適合這行呢 真的
I think you'd be great at it. Really.
我會愿意買任何你賣的東西
I'd buy anything from you.
我現在都在考慮去漂白我的牙了呢
I'm thinking about getting my chompers bleached,
那還只是剩下一半的你的廣告牌呢
and there's only half of you up there.
-真的嗎 -真的
- Really? - Yeah.
問自己下一步該走向哪其實挺令人恐懼
It can be scary to ask yourself what's next.
心里會浮現所有對自己的質疑
All the doubts start to creep in.
別人會喜歡我嗎
Are people going to like me?
還好燙[火辣]啊
Ooh, still hot.
謝謝夸獎
Thank you!
我每周都會找幾天在后院健健身
I throw a tractor tire around the backyard a couple days a week.
我能克服困難嗎
Can I handle the challenge?
兄弟
Dude.
你可以不停地對自己提出質疑
You can ask these questions forever,
但你也可以踏出第一步
or you can just take the first step.
所有的房屋開放日都有這五點檢查要素
Here is your five-point checklist for any open house.
第一點
Number one --
抱歉 教授
Sorry, professor.
菲爾 親愛的 你來這里做什么呢
Phil, honey. What are you doing here?
我來給你個驚喜 順便約你去吃晚飯嘛
Hey. I thought I'd surprise you and take you out to dinner.
突發奇想 你知道我就喜歡這樣
Spontaneous. You know I like that.
我先去確認一下大家都走了沒
Well, um, let me just make sure everybody's gone.
拿上我的包就可以鎖門了
I'll grab my bag and lock up.
沒問題
Awesome.
我能對你的服裝提供協助嗎[幫你脫衣服]
May I help you with your clothes?
看來這里真的只剩下我們了
I guess we are the only ones here.
或許我們先從褲子開始吧
Perhaps we'll start with the pants.
通常你都是喜歡...
Normally, you like a little...
慢慢解開襯衫扣子的
...slow shirt unbuttoning,
但看來今天我們... 要直搗黃龍啦
but I guess we... are cutting to the chase.
爸 你還在找地方放你的屁股嗎
Dad. Are you still looking for a place to leave that butt?
真的好惡心
It's so gross.
論建立辦公室情誼
There's nothing better for office comradery
沒有比惡作劇更棒的方法了
than a practical joke.
能振奮人心呢
It lifts people' spirits.
我輸了
Well played.